<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on CircuitWall IT Consultancy</title>
    <link>circuitwall.com/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on CircuitWall IT Consultancy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="circuitwall.com/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>circuitwall.com/services/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>circuitwall.com/services/about/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Andrew Wu, live and work in Stockholm Sweden.
I am an individual consultant with extensive experience in Java, Bigdata and Machine learning. My services including but not limited to:
 Java service development Big data &amp;amp; Machine learning Cloud technologies (public and private)  Contact me if you need a hand or advices, and you are welcome to add me to your Linkedin contact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big data &amp; Machine learning</title>
      <link>circuitwall.com/services/bigdataml/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>circuitwall.com/services/bigdataml/</guid>
      <description>Technologies supporting big data and machine learning like hadoop are more than 10 years old. If you think big data is a buzz word, then you are falling behind.
Big data and machine learning is about three things in my mind:
 Ability to fetch and store large number of data. Ability to analyze big data efficently. Ability to use the data and enpower your business.  Key competences and Technologies</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud technologie</title>
      <link>circuitwall.com/services/goingcloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>circuitwall.com/services/goingcloud/</guid>
      <description>Alright, &amp;ldquo;Cloud&amp;rdquo; is a real buzz word. Some people understand is the cloud drive, on-demand virtual machines, or the stuff floating on the sky&amp;hellip; I say cloud is all those combined with out the floating stuff of course.
Key competences and Technologies
 AWS EC2 &amp;amp; VPC Cloudfoundry  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java Development</title>
      <link>circuitwall.com/services/ApplicationDevelopment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>circuitwall.com/services/ApplicationDevelopment/</guid>
      <description>Ten years of professional experience tought me how to build maintainable and performant service. I deliver any part of a service, front-end and back.
Key competences and Technologies
 Java SE/EE Spring, Springboot Javascript, CSS REST API MySQL, MongoDB, Riak  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>